{"data":{"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","address":"7650 Gratiot Ave","zipcode":"48213","owner":"Mr. Anani","licenseNumber":"217912","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","mostRecentLicenseDate":"5/8/2018","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Permanently Closed","riskCategory":null,"reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","geom":"0101000020E61000002C09F79A03C154C0F84A8A7632304540","inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"43862","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","inspectionDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"2","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"2","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"43862","inspectionDate":"10/24/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"WALK-IN FREEZER","subLocation":"Inside the Walk-in freezer","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"43862","inspectionDate":"10/24/2018","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM (EMPLOYEE)","subLocation":"Missing Hand washing signage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-10-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"}]},{"inspectionid":"40610","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","inspectionDate":"2017-10-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"1","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"1","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"40610","inspectionDate":"10/30/2017","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.12","violationDescription":"(A) PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be cleaned as often as necessary to keep them clean.\r\n(B) Except spill cleanup, cleaning shall be done during periods when the least amount of FOOD is exposed such as after closing. ","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities/structures","subItem":"floors","problemDescription":"With accumulation of debris","subProblem":"","location":"MOP SINK AREA","subLocation":"On the floor Debris","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2017-10-30T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Keep clean."}]},{"inspectionid":"36606","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","inspectionDate":"2016-09-19T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"0","ccount":"4","criticalcount":"0","noncritical":"4","correctedcritical":"0","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36606","inspectionDate":"9/19/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"Floor(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"REAR STORAGE ROOM","subLocation":"At the Floor tiles","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36606","inspectionDate":"9/19/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Broken","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"Around the Windows","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36606","inspectionDate":"9/19/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"REAR AREA","subLocation":"Around the Wall(s)","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36606","inspectionDate":"9/19/2016","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FRONT AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"36038","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","inspectionDate":"2016-08-02T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","inspectorid":"87","pcount":"0","pfcount":"2","ccount":"6","criticalcount":"2","noncritical":"6","correctedcritical":"2","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"disposable, paper towels","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Paper toweling","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"5-501.17","violationDescription":"A toilet room used by females shall be provided with a covered receptacle for sanitary napkins.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Covered waste receptacle(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"No Covered waste container","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide as required"},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-303.11","violationDescription":"Light of the proper intensity shall be provided as specified.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Lighting intensity","subItem":"at work levels","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the Lights","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Maintain in good repair"},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.111","violationDescription":"The presence of insects, rodents, and other pests shall be controlled to minimize their presence on the PREMISES.  by:\r\n(A) Routinely inspecting incoming shipments of FOOD and supplies; \r\n(B) Routinely inspecting the PREMISES for evidence of pests;\r\n(C) Using methods, if pests are found, such as trapping devices or other means of pest control as specified.(Pf) \r\n(D) Eliminating harborage conditions. \r\n","violationType":"Foundation","criticalViolationType":"Yes","itemDescription":"Routine inspections","subItem":"of premises for evidence of pests","problemDescription":"Not performed","subProblem":"","location":"HOT WATER TANK AREA","subLocation":"Around the Pest droppings","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Inspections must be performed as stated above."},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Equipment components","subItem":"","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Around the Equipment","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-201.17","violationDescription":"(A) Except as otherwise allowed by law, attachments to walls and ceilings such as light fixtures, mechanical room ventilation system components, vent covers, wall mounted fans, decorative items, and other attachments shall be EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) In a CONSUMER area, wall and ceiling surfaces and decorative items and attachments that are provided for ambiance need not meet this requirement if they are kept clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Wall attachment(s)","subItem":"vent covers","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Ceiling vent cover(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"Open seams","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"At the BASEBOARD","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2016-08-12T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace."},{"inspectionid":"36038","inspectionDate":"8/2/2016","inspectionType":"Preopening/COO","establishmentid":"1548","name":"Anani ","violationCode":"6-501.11","violationDescription":"PHYSICAL FACILITIES shall be maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","criticalViolationType":"No","itemDescription":"Physical facilities","subItem":"wall(s)","problemDescription":"In poor repair","subProblem":"","location":"RESTAURANT","subLocation":"Missing Electrical outlet wall cover","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]}]}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"1548"}}